convert-to.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy at convert-to.com

**Privacy policy**

Privacy Policy for **convert-to.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by **email: hobbymaker@gmail.com**

At **convert-to.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by **convert-to.com** and how the information is used. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit and use **convert-to.com** web site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Cookies make website visits more convenient by improved functionality. Cookies are part of a method of tracking information you enter on a web site using a file on your computer. We do use a cookie to log whether you have visited the site already before. No personal information is written to the cookie at all. It is primarily used to save you time by automatically populating contact forms, forms in our Blog, discussion forum, and other locations on the site.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site:

Our advertising partners include **[Google Adsense – http://www.google.com/adsense/](http://www.google.com/adsense/ "Google Adsense program.")** and **DoubleClick DART**. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our web site, these are to improve visitors online experience including displaying of more relevant ads relating to the site’s content. Visitors may opt-out of the use of the **DoubleClick** cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy info page at the following URL:   
**<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>**

Currently, **convert-to.com** has also other relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks:

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on **convert-to.com** directly to your browsers. These automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you can see.

Please note that **convert-to.com** privacy practices as described on this page do not apply to the privacy policies or practices of other businesses and websites. **convert-to.com** has no access to, or control over, these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. These matters are very common to the web and always evolving, but if you wish to learn or just to find out more, please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **convert-to.com** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Site Tracking – Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **convert-to.com** makes use of log files. We use **[Google Analytics – http://www.google.com/analytics/](http://www.google.com/analytics/ "Google's Analytics program.")** program. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Email Addresses**  
We log your email address in only in these situations: Newsletter purpose, contact/email-reply purpose, when posting comment to a Blog post. The email addresses are never shared.

**Out-going Links to other websites  
**Our site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policy and practices or, the content of any other web site linked from **convert-to.com** site.

##### Find pages on convert to with online Google Custom Search

For online collaboration to improve the _» Privacy policy_ , requests for new units or web tools additions, send your feedback.

No comments yet.
